制暴：无限杀机
* 翻译：三块一毛七 / 微博：三块一毛七x *
本字幕仅供交流学习，请勿用于商业用途；转载请注明出处，请勿删除译者信息
- 老大 这是给你的 - 不 不 不 别这样
- Boss. This for you. - No, no, no. Come on.
我不能压榨你的家人
I can't impose on your family.
不
No.
雅思敏 这是她给你做的
Yasmin, she made this just for you.
头 拜托
Jefe, please.
收下吧
Take it.
替我对她说声谢谢
Tell her thank you.
好
Yeah.
大家听着
So, listen.
今天任务繁重
Today's gonna be hard.
一整天都会有人来检查
We got inspections all day.
这边建东西那边拆两下都需要填表格
Forms to build, forms to break down
还有各种货物挡路
and deliveries all gettin' in our way.
今天努力工作
We work hard today,
奖金就少不了你们的
there'll be a bonus for ya.
明白吗
Understand?
希望大家回家时
And let's all go home
十根手指都还能完好无损
with the same amount of fingers that we came with.
好了
All right.
兄弟们
Hermanos.
大吉大利事事顺意 加油
Have a good day. Let's get it.
加西亚家庭建筑公司
- 早啊 杰茜 - 早上好 列文
- Morning, Jess. - Buenos dias, Levon.
- 你好吗 - 我很好
- How you doing? - I'm good.
- 谢谢 - 嘿 列文
- Gracias. - Hey, Levon.
今天没人找你要钱吗
No one's been asking you for money today?
没有
No.
- 怎么这么问 - 因为很显然
- Why? - Because, apparently,
我是这个家里唯一一个
I am the only person in the family
会处理供应商账目的人
who can do the vendor accounting.
瞧你这话说的
Oh, excuse me!
看来我们成了恶毒父母了 对吧 亲爱的
Hey, I guess we're evil parents, babe, huh?
因为我们押着她做了几个小时工作
'Cause we make her work a couple hours.
至少别今天吧
Not today.
你不如抓紧把那些垫付款算清
How about you get those disbursements done, huh?
外面还有一排排的卡车等着拿工资
We got a line of trucks out there that need paying.
你可以给我工资
You could pay me.
给你工资干什么
Pay you for what?
因为我们这19年免费管你住
For 19 years of free rent,
管你吃 供你上高中
and groceries, and high school,
上大学 买化妆品 学空手道吗
college, makeup, karate classes?
- 你想让我继续说吗 - 不是吧 算了别说了
- You want me to keep goin'? - Really? No. It's okay.
列文 你可以签一下吗 拜托了
Levon, can you sign that, please?
- 老爸 - 干嘛
- Dad? - What?
- 今天太糟心了 - 我知道
- Today is a total shitshow. - I know.
你一次性给我安排了三件事
And you scheduled three things at once.
她说得没错
She's not wrong.
您好 这里是加西亚家庭建筑公司
Hi, yeah. This is Garcia and Family Construction.
对 我是卡拉
Yeah, you're speaking with Carla,
你已经让我等了一会了
you've had me on hold for a bit now.
所以那批货今天会送到 对吗
So, we're gettin' those deliveries today, right?
好 我等着
Yeah, I'll hold.
今晚我要用这么多钱
This is what I need for tonight.
你疯了 这是什么 你要办婚礼还是咋的
That's insane. What is that? Is that for your wedding or something?
不 就是今晚要用的
No, it's for tonight.
这学期结束了 所以我们要庆祝一下
We finished the semester, so we're gonna celebrate.
我是说 你才读完了一个学期
I mean, you just finished one semester.
- 是啊 很重要的一个里程碑 - 是吗
- Right. It's a big milestone. - Is it?
- 是的 - 有这回事吗
- Yes. - Is that a thing?
听着 本来还要花的钱还要更多
Look, it could be worse, okay?
- 是这样的 大家在集资 - 嗯
- Look, I'm passing the hat. - Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- 这钱是用来一辆派对车 - 我的天
- That gets us a party van. - Oh, my God.
晚餐订一个私人包间
Locks in a private room for dinner.
这也太省钱了
Just saving like crazy.
对啊 我只需要一张信用卡做登记
Yeah. I just need a card on file.
米娅 不行 我不…
Mija, I can't. I don't...
米娅…
Mija...
好吧 不用就不用
Okay, fine. I don't need it.
她想要什么给她就是了
Just give her what she wants.
不 妈妈 我可以替自己说话
No, Mom, I can fight my own battles.
不 不 不 我没说不给
Oh, no, no, nobody's arguing that.
毕竟每个人都需要一辆派对巴士 对吧
I mean, everybody needs a party bus, right?
在他们读完一个学期后 给你
After they finish one semester. Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 凯特
Hey, Kate.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
他得回去工作了
He needs to get back to work.
他妈的滚一边去 关你屁事
Get the fuck out of here. It's not your business.
我没事 头儿
I'm good, boss.
没事的 就五分钟
All good. Five minutes.
嘿
Hey!
等等 放下你们的武器
Hold on. Put down your weapons.
我尊重你们
I was respectful.
你们却不尊重我
You weren't.
滚出去 起来
Get outta here. Get up.
别再回来
Don't come back.
- 哥几个撤吧 - 我们撤[西语]
- Vamonos. - Vamonos.
没大碍吧
You okay?
你是怎么做到的
How did you do that?
我们该回去工作了
We need to get back to work.
这一个 装在右侧
This one. Over to the right.
- 没问题 - 谢了 凯特
- You got it. - Thanks, Kate.
列文 我滴妈呀
Levon! Holy fuck!
你那些是军队里学的吗
Was that some military shit?
你什么都没看到
You didn't see anything.
要是我爸知道了 他肯定会大吃一惊
If Dad knew, he'd shit bricks.
你可以教我吗
Can you teach me?
我爷爷以前当过伞兵
Look, my grandpa, he was a paratrooper.
他教我怎么掰断手指
Taught me how to break fingers,
追踪动物
track animals.
掰断手指
Break fingers?
是啊
Yeah.
奶奶给你做了廷加 鸡肉碎
Grandma made you tinga. Shredded chicken.
味道很不错
It's good.
她给你准备了手工制作的玉米饼
And Grandma made you some handmade grandma tortillas.
为什么大家都想投喂我
Why is everyone always feeding me?
要是大家不投喂 你就只能吃金枪鱼罐头和花生酱了
If we don't, you'll just eat canned tuna and peanut butter.
你什么都没看到 知道了吗
You didn't see anything, okay?
告密者天打雷劈
Snitches get stitches.
只是我有需要时你得罩着我
Just get my back if I ever need it.
没问题 珍妮
Sure, Jenny.
拜拜
See ya.
爱你 爸爸
Love you, Daddy.
我也爱你 宝贝 到车上去
Love you, too, honey. Get in the truck.
有什么大事吗
What's the occasion?
没什么大事
No occasion.
梅瑞狄斯在招待朋友
Meredith's entertaining some friends.
嗯
Yeah.
我不知道你今天要来探视
I didn't realize today was your visitation.
你可以让她留下来
You could let her stay.
拜托 罗斯医生 大家没必要闹得这么难堪
Yeah, please, Doctor Roth, we don't have to do this.
她妈妈需要你的时候你不在
You weren't there when her mother needed you
梅瑞狄斯需要你的时候你也不会在她身边
and you won't be there when Meredith needs you,
但我会
but I will.
我知道
Oh, I know.
你想揍我
You want to strike me.
你也只会这样了
It's your only answer.
暴力手段
Violence.
你作为家长危险至极
You're an unsafe parent.
你是一个杀手
You're a killer.
这你掩盖不了
You can't pretend that you're not.
先走一步了 罗斯医生
Excuse me, Doctor Roth.
今天是我探视的日子
Today's my day.
你爷爷为什么要在我的探视日开派对
Why's your grandfather throwing a party on my day?
我没吃东西 快饿死了
I'm super hungry. I didn't eat.
我在等你
I was waiting for you.
是吗
You were?
嗯
Yeah.
好吧 咱们走
Okay. Let's go.
- 给你 - 谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- 谢谢 - 慢用
- Thank you. - Enjoy.
你不用给我买礼物
I don't need you buying stuff.
来吧 拆礼物
Come on. Open it.
是妈妈
It's Mama.
我用我爸给我的胶卷相机拍了这张照片
I took that picture with a film camera my dad gave me.
爷爷把妈妈的照片全都拿了下来
Grandpa took all of Mama's pictures down.
有时候我都忘了她的样子
Sometimes I forget what she looks like.
她长得很像你
She looks like you.
爸爸 我可以跟你说件事吗
Dad, can I tell you something?
什么都行
Anything.
我在生妈妈的气
I'm mad at Mama.
因为她去世了 抛下我们
For dying and leaving us.
没关系
It's okay.
我也很难过
I hurt, too.
马特现在可以见你了
Matt will see you now.
他在我探视期间给她开派对
He's throwing parties for her during my visitation time.
看着我 嘲笑我
Staring at me, laughing.
他在给你下套
He's baiting you.
希望你能打他一拳
Hoping you throw a punch.
我才不打
Nah.
那样他就赢了
Then he wins.
对方律师声称你因服役患上了未经治疗的
Opposing counsel alleges you have untreated PTSD
创伤后应激障碍和脑损伤
and brain trauma from your military service,
让你存在暴力行为的风险
making you at-risk for violence.
我生在英国 为这个国家鞠躬尽瘁22年
I served Britain, the country of my birth, for 22 years.
现在反倒成了坏人不成
I'm the fuckin' bad guy for it?
不止如此
It gets worse.
他们要求监视需在监督下进行
They're requesting supervised visits
并将探视时间从每周两小时
and a reduction in visitation from two hours a week
缩短到每两周一小时
to one hour every two.
我必须反抗
I have to fight this.
我存了一万美元
I have ten grand saved up.
可你还睡在卡车里
From sleeping in your truck?
法庭对你没有固定居所不会高兴的
Court won't be thrilled by your lack of a fixed residence.
嘿 我会搞定的
Hey, I'll figure it out.
罗斯医生为什么这么恨你
Why does Doctor Roth hate you so much?
他认为我杀了他女儿
He thinks I killed his daughter.
是你杀的吗
Did you?
她是自杀
It was suicide.
我当时在海外执行任务
I was overseas on a deployment.
她这辈子都在和抑郁症作斗争
She battled depression her whole life.
你们听说过消耗战吗
You've heard of attrition warfare?
慢慢将敌人消耗殆尽
Yeah. You grind the enemy down slowly.
这家伙有一个团队
This guy's got a team
每小时收费上千美元
of thousand-dollar-an-hour attorneys
不把你榨得倾家荡产、灰飞烟灭决不罢休
who will bleed you dry until you turn to dust and blow away.
我们的最佳策略是谈判投降
The best we can do is negotiated surrender.
你有女儿吗
You have a daughter?
我给你们带了点好东西
I got you guys a little somethin'.
妮娜
Nina.
乔斯林…
Jocelyn...
- 尚特尔 还有露比 - 谢了 姐妹
- Chantel. And Rubi. - Thanks, Mama.
姐们 这也太牛逼了
Dude, these are insane!
你从哪弄来的
Where'd you get these?
我有个表弟 或者说七个
I have a cousin. Or seven.
干杯 姐妹们
Salud , bitches!
谢谢
Thank you.
干杯
Shots.
嘿
Hey!
什么 什么
What? What? What?
我们他妈还在这里干什么
What the fuck are we still doing here?
他说他要那个人
He said he wants the One.
“我要那个人 我他妈就要那个人”
"I want the One. I want the fucking One."
这他妈是什么意思
What the fuck does that mean?
他见到她之后自然会知道 好吗
He'll know it when he sees her, okay?
你知道把这单做完
Do you know how much fuckin' money
我们能挣多少钱吗
we're gonna make on this?
- 最好是 - 好好享受吧
- We better. - Enjoy, yeah?
最后一家店
Hey, last establishment.
你们明天还要搭早班机
You guys have early flights.
后面的桌子还空着吗
Is that back table open?
告诉我你名字就是你的了
It's yours if you tell me your name.
珍妮
It's Jenny.
你好 我是约翰尼
Hi, I'm Johnny.
你好 约翰尼
Hi, Johnny.
那边
Right here.
好兄弟
My man.
你比一份PPT更加重要
You are more than a pitch deck.
妮娜
Nina?
- 妮娜 别吐出来 - 我没事
- Nina, don't throw up. - I'm fine.
她一副要吐了的样子
She's making her puke face.
我带你去洗手间
Let's get you to a bathroom.
便宜货 晦气
Cheap! Bad energy.
天哪
Oh, my God.
你太可恨了 这一点不好笑
I hate you so much right now, it's not funny.
还是有点好笑的
It's kinda funny.
天哪 我看上去像个疯婆子
Oh, my God, I look mad busted.
我不能这样子出去见人
I cannot go out there like this.
省省力气吧 30分钟我们就得走了
Okay, well, pick your battles, 'cause we're leavin' in 30.
操
Fuck!
快走
Go.
珍妮失踪了
Jenny's missing.
什么叫“失踪了”
What do you mean, "missing"?
星期五她和朋友出去玩
She went out with her friends on Friday.
星期六我们有点担心
Saturday, we were worried,
所以我们报了警 然后到了星期天…
so we called the cops, and then on Sunday...
星期天晚上她有一场钢琴演奏会
She had a piano recital on Sunday night.
我们邀请了家族里一半的人
We invited half our family.
我表妹迪诺拉是费城的警队队长
My cousin Dinora is a Police Captain in Philly,
她说他们不办理这种案子
and she says they don't work these cases.
他们做个记录 然后就不管了
They take a report and forget about it.
你可以帮我们吗
Can you help us?
我可以维持工地的正常运作
I can keep the site running smoothly.
不 帮我们找到珍妮
No. Help us find Jen.
我爸曾经是一名绿色贝雷帽
My dad was a Green Beret.
美国陆军特种部队
你们这类人我隔着一英里都能认出来
I can see you guys comin' a mile away.
你们抓捕坏人
You hunt bad guys.
飞机跳伞
You jump outta planes.
抓住那些坏蛋
And you get those bad guys.
我现在不是那个人了
I'm a different person now.
好吧
All right, well,
也许这能打动你
maybe this'll help her.
这里是五万
Here, it's 50.
拿着
Take it.
我们还另外付你2万作为费用
We have another 20 for expenses.
拿着啊 伙计
Come on, just take it, man.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我已经不干那种事了
It's not who I am anymore.
枪叔 是我啊
Gunny, it's me!
不要杀我
Don't kill me!
我带了牛排
I got steaks!
你要是往左偏一英尺 我已经当场身亡了
If you'd shot a foot to the left, I'd be dead.
如果我要杀你 你绝对活不了
If I wanted you dead, you'd be dead.
你知道 对我来说
You know, for me,
白天黑夜没有区别
there's no separation between day and night.
所以我就自己开辟出白天黑夜
So, I got to make my own.
生活在一个灰暗的世界里不容易
It's hard livin' in a gray world.
我没能保住你的眼睛
I couldn't save your eyes.
对不起
Sorry.
我很难过
That eats at me.
不
No.
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
如果不是你赶来 把我抱起来跑开
Joyce would be burying tags in the back yard
乔伊斯现在就会在后院埋葬我的铭牌
if you hadn't come along, scooped me up and ran.
她叫什么名字
What's her name?
珍妮
Jenny.
珍妮 好
Jenny. All right.
她是好孩子吗
She a good kid?
非常好
She's a great kid.
既然你决定了要干 最好全力以赴
Now, you do this, you better lock in.
不遗余力 绝不能半途而废
You better go full on, no half-measures.
但如果你做到了 上帝保佑
But you do, God help 'em.
我告诉过珍妮我会罩着她
I told Jenny I had her back.
好吧…
Well, uh...
我想念你
I miss ya.
我担心你
I worry about ya,
但你已经下定决心的事
but you didn't have to come down here and pretend that
就不用专程跑来假装征求我的同意
you needed my permission for something you already made your mind up about.
快进来 晚饭好了
Get in here. We're eating.
嘿 卡拉
Hey, Carla.
谢谢你能来
Thanks for coming.
他在哪
Where is he?
楼上 左边第一扇门
Upstairs. First door on your left.
《月光奏鸣曲》
"Moonlight Sonata".
- 嗯 - 很动听
- Yeah. - It's beautiful.
她拒绝了音乐奖学金
She turned down a music scholarship
去上商学院
to go to business school.
她想继承她老爸的衣钵
She wanted to be like her pops.
成为地产大亨
Be a big land developer.
她一定会成功
And she will.
嗯
Yeah.
不了 谢谢
Nah. No, thanks.
你的家人需要顶梁柱
Your family needs hope.
但我不能这样面对他们
But I can't face 'em like this.
我妻子过世后
When my wife passed,
我离开了海军陆战队
and I left the Royal Marines,
换做别人可能早就觉得我不可救药
a lot of people would've given up on me.
但你们对我很耐心
But you were patient with me.
- 你 卡拉 珍妮 - 珍妮
- You, Carla, Jenny. - Jenny.
你们是我的家人
You're my family.
看着我 兄弟
Look at me, brother.
我会把她带回家
I'm gonna bring her home.
我保证
I promise.
我会把她带回家
I'm gonna bring her home.
“斯基普酒吧”
"Skip's Bar."
非常感谢 还好吗 老兄
Thank you very much. Good, bro?
你好吗 是吗
You good? Yeah?
你好吗
How you doing?
你需要来点开胃酒 知道吗
You need a little aperitif, you know?
好
All right.
走错屋了 小子
Oh, yo. Wrong house, kid.
滚出去
Get the fuck out.
你好 约翰尼
Hello, Johnny.
要比比看吗 看谁的枪更快
Wanna have a race? See who wins?
手举起来 站起来
Hands up. Stand up.
双手抱头
Place your fingers behind your head.
你警察吗
You a cop?
我要是警察就好了
You wish I was a cop.
你开心就好 小子
Your adventure, kid.
女孩在哪
Where's the girl?
什么女孩
What girl?
失踪女孩
The missing girl.
你朋友在酒吧后面绑走的那个
The one your friends snatched outta the back of the bar.
我跟警察都说过了 她跑掉了 喝醉了还是什么的
I told the cops. She ran off. Drunk or somethin'.
那傻妞连酒瓶都拿不稳
Fuckin' poobutt can't hold her drink.
这也能赖我吗
How's that my problem?
人们会撒谎
People lie.
你撒谎了吗 约翰尼
Do you lie, Johnny?
我不相信人们
I don't trust people.
但我相信生物学
I trust biology.
人的神经回路都是一样的
We're all wired the same.
给我他妈的起来
Get the fuck up.
操你妈
Fuck you.
你的大脑知道你在浴缸里
Your mind knows you're in the bathtub
也知道这只是一条湿毛巾
and it's just a wet towel.
但肾上腺素让你心跳加速
But adrenaline makes your heart race,
所以你会消耗更多的氧气
so you burn more air.
你的神经系统会告诉你你在溺水
Your nervous system tells you that you're drowning.
你老板知道你在吧台贩毒吗
Your bosses know you deal dope over the bar top?
从收银机里偷钱
Steal from the till?
去你的
Fuck you!
你知道那帮人都是狠人
You know these guys are next level.
动不动就灭你九族
They wipe out entire fucking bloodlines.
那好吧
Fair enough.
你今天必须告诉我名字
Just know you're giving me names.
敬酒罚酒你自己选
Your choice how.
约翰尼
Johnny?
你在哪 兄弟
Where are you, brother?
你在等人吗
You're expecting company?
他妈的想不到吧
Damn fuckin' right, I am.
开门 否则我杀了你
Open the door. Fuckin' kill you.
俄罗斯人
Russians.
妈的
Fuck.
对不起 妈妈
I'm sorry, Mom.
很抱歉…
I'm sorry for...
我总是躲在成就背后保护自己
shielding myself in a blanket of accomplishments.
真希望你能看到…
I wish you could've seen me...
真实的我
who I really am.
只想和你一样强大
Just want to be strong like you.
我来这里干嘛
What am I doing here?
你最好亲眼看看 老大
It's better you see for yourself, boss.
不是什么大事
It's not a big problem.
你们俩傻逼又干了什么
What the fuck have you two done, huh?
他们为什么朝对方开枪
Why'd they shoot each other?
这太不专业了
This is very unprofessional.
约翰尼做事没个分寸 一点骨气都没有
Johnny has no control. He's a weak man.
可能他一时胡言乱语 然后就是砰砰两声
Maybe he talk crazy, and then it's bang-bang time.
- “砰砰” - 是啊
- "Bang-bang time"? - Yeah.
砰砰
Bang-bang time.
你发现有什么不同了吗
You notice anything different?
你的发型
Your hair.
傻逼
Idiot.
我的钱他妈的在哪
Where is my fucking money?
你觉得这是抢劫
You think this was a robbery?
不可能
Impossible.
谁会抢劫我们 没有人那么蠢
No one would rob us. No one is that stupid,
或者那么疯
or that crazy.
这是霰弹枪枪伤
This is a shotgun wound.
你看到霰弹枪了吗
You see any shotguns?
九捆现金不见了
That's nine bands missing.
我们的九万美元就这样他妈的没了
Ninety thousand dollars of our fucking money!
那是西蒙的钱
It's Symon's money.
愿你的鲜血净化这片土地 朋友
May your blood purify the soil, comrade.
芝加哥专业清洁服务
嘿 亲爱的
Hey, sweetheart.
嘿 爸爸 你在做什么
Hey, Daddy, what are you doing?
没什么 就是…
Uh, nothin'. Just, uh...
忙点工作
Just some work.
- 你在学校吗 - 嗯
- Are you in school? - Yeah.
你应该在学校里给我打电话吗
You supposed to be calling me from school?
不应该
No.
一切还好吗
Everything okay?
嗯 我只想打个招呼 爱你爸爸
Yeah, I just wanted to say, "hi." Love you, Daddy.
我也爱你
Love you, too.
拜
Bye.
车门会他妈的自己打开吗
The fucking door opens itself?
他妈的全乱套了
Everything is fucked!
我不喜欢这样
I don't like this.
一整晚床上就我一个人
I'm alone in the bed all night.
你吃点东西
You eat.
然后就到床上休息一会
You come to bed for a bit.
你以为钱是天上掉下来的吗
You think the money falls from the sky?
混账东西
Bastard.
希望你不介意
Hope you don't mind.
我饿了
I was hungry.
我们来聊聊
Thought we could have a little chat.
我会把胶带撕掉
I'm gonna take the tape off.
但如果你控制不了自己的音量…
But if you can't control your volume...
你就水里待着去吧
You go in the water.
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
我应该知道吗
Should I?
你显然不知道你惹上的是什么人
You clearly have no idea who you fuck with.
你高兴就好 说吧
Make yourself happy. Tell me.
你听说过我们吗
You have heard of us?
听说过
I have.
真的吗
Really?
盗贼
The Vor.
布拉瓦特 兄弟会
The Bratva. The Brothers.
盗贼联盟
The League of Thieves.
俄罗斯黑帮现在怎么自称都行
Whatever Russian gangsters like to call themselves these days.
看来你有点来头
You clearly are somebody.
你杀了兄弟会的士兵
You slaughter Vory soldiers.
你偷了兄弟会的钱
You steal Vory money.
一场误会罢了
It was a misunderstanding.
我是兄弟会高层人员
I am a brother of high rank.
你和所有与你有关的人
You and all connected with you,
三代之内不死不休
will be hunted for three generations.
嗯 我想也是
Yep. I assumed so.
我们都知道下场会怎样
We all know how these things play out
如果你们把事情搞砸
if you don't keep them tidy.
去你妈的
Fuck you!
这巴掌是因为你今早打了那个女人
That's for slapping that woman this morning.
那女人是我老婆
That woman was my wife.
这巴掌是因为你打老婆
That's for slapping your wife.
这是你的钱
Here's your money.
我不是小偷
I'm not a thief.
我对你的生意没兴趣
I don't care about your business.
我在找一个姑娘
I'm lookin' for a young lady.
我…我搞不懂
I... I don't understand.
那间你用来做肮脏勾当的酒吧
The bar you do your dirty business out of,
有一个19岁的女孩被绑架了
a 19 year-old girl was kidnapped.
我在找她
I'm lookin' for her.
迪米
Dimi.
也许你该小点声
Maybe you should keep your voice down.
你想怎样
What do you want?
把女孩交出来
Gimme the girl,
大家井水不犯河水
and everybody goes about their business.
一个女孩
A girl?
这么大费周章就为了一个女孩
All of this is for a girl?
没人会为了卖一个女人杀掉三个人
No one kills three people to sell a woman.
没人
No one.
我不是要卖她
I'm not selling her.
我要带她回家
I'm gonna bring her home.
不达目的誓不罢休
Not stopping until I do.
你是谁
Who are you?
你是什么东西
What are you?
去你妈的
Fuck you.
Fuck you!
行吧 玩够了
Okay, we're done.
迪米
Dimi.
你是谁 迪米
Who are you, Dimi?
父亲
Father.
他拿走钱
He takes money.
又把钱留下
He leaves money.
他杀人不眨眼
He kills without fear.
问题是为什么
The question is why?
他受人尊敬 为人体面
Wolo was a respected man of honor,
但他儿子跟我们不是一路人
but his son was never like us.
迪米不是生意人
Dimi is not a businessman.
成天胡闹 无心工作
He prefers mischief over hard work.
每天他妈的都在践踏他父亲的苦心
He spits on his father's heart every fucking day.
找出这个人
Find this man.
把他带给我
And bring him to me.
我叫珍妮·加西亚
My name is Jenny Garcia.
我爸爸是乔·加西亚
My father is Joe.
我妈妈是卡拉·加西亚
My mother is Carla.
你们找错人了 你们搞错了
You have the wrong girl. This is a mistake.
他们不是真的
They're not real.
你不是真的
You're not real.
这…
This...
他妈的是真的
is fucking real.
吃你的饭
Eat your fuckin' food,
然后把衣服穿上
then you put on the fucking clothes
- 乖乖把嘴闭上 - 去你的
- and shut the fuck up! - Fuck you!
你之前见过人死的样子吗
Have you ever seen someone die before?
他们的眼睛会立刻蒙上一层阴霾
Their eyes just cloud right over.
你真是个可人的东西
You're so fuckin' pretty. Huh?
是吗 大小姐
Aren't you, Princess?
砰
Boop.
吃你的饭
Eat your fuckin' food!
据悉
Believe the idea the
白袜队正在认真商讨
White Sox are in serious talks
在南环区的78号地块
to build a new stadium in the South Loops, The 78,
即芝加哥河畔、罗斯福路旁的位置新建一座体育场
the location by the Chicago River just off Roosevelt.
对于南环区认真推进新球场建设谈判的计划
I love the idea of being in serious talks
我表示非常支持
for a new stadium in the South Loop.
美国司法部
缉毒局
最近怎么样 老兄 搞承包发家致富了吧
How's it goin', cat? Getting rich contracting?
是啊 整天灌水泥罢了
Oh, yeah. Pouring concrete more like.
早就金盆洗手了 现在是个老老实实的纳税人
I'm outta the game. I'm an honest taxpayer now.
你和枪叔见过了吧 他怎么样
You talked to Gunny? How's he doing?
前几天去见了他 日子过得很滋润
Saw him the other day. He's happy.
无事不登三宝殿
Well, you never call me unless you need something,
所以你要我做什么
so, what do you want?
我要找一个叫迪米的人
Lookin' for someone called Dimi.
可能叫迪米特里 沃罗迪迈尔·科利斯尼克的同伙
Probably Dimitri. An associate of Wolodymyr Kolisnyk.
那可是个大人物 兄弟
That's a high-ranking dude, cat.
黑手党头目
Mafia captain.
正儿八经的俄罗斯黑手党扛把子
Legit Bratva shot caller.
这种人不好惹
Not a guy you wanna fuck with.
那当然
Nah, never.
这个叫迪米的家伙
This Dimi fella,
他可能涉嫌人口贩卖
he might be involved in human trafficking.
你可以在NADDIS和NCIC检索一下吗 看能不能找到他
Can you check NADDIS and NCIC? See if you can get a hit?
NADDIS：缉毒局数据库
NCIC：联邦犯罪信息库
我得小心行事
I gotta be careful,
但朱丽叶市有一家海蒂酒吧
but there's a bar called Hattie's in Joliet,
他们在那里替俄罗斯人卖冰毒
where they sell meth for the Russians.
也许你应该去那里喝杯酒
Maybe you should get a beer there.
不错 谢了
Nice one. Thanks.
嘿 喝点什么
Hey. Whatcha havin'?
给我来杯啤酒 你做主
I'll just have a beer. You pick.
行啊
Okay.
嘿 好久不见啊 最近干啥去了
Oh, hey, stranger. Where you been?
忙着赚钱
Tryin' to make a buck.
你知道
You know,
听说你和你那混账哥哥
rumor has it you and your shitbag brother
一直在和俄罗斯人打交道
have been talkin' to the Russians.
听说你磕嗨了
Rumor has it you were so high,
在一个毒窝里不小心杀了大麦克
you accidentally killed Big Mike in a trap house
还栽赃给抢劫团伙
and blamed it on a robbery crew.
他妈的闭嘴 他妈的…
Fuckin' shut up. Fuckin'...
要是达奇发现有人背着他跟俄罗斯人接触
Dutch finds out anybody's talkin' to the Russians but him,
他他妈的非得气疯不可
he's gonna lose his fuckin' mind.
你认识这个人吗
Do you know this guy?
不认识 从没见过
No. I've never seen him.
我不喜欢他
I don't like him.
像个警察
Looks like a cop.
他口袋里有把枪
He's got a gun in his pocket.
像是点38口径 看到了吗
Like a .38. You see it?
妈的 还真是
Fuck. Yes.
你有活干了 小子
You're up, kid.
跟我来
Follow me.
去和那个人谈谈
Go talk to the man.
你在找东西吗
You lookin' for somethin'?
我只对制药感兴趣 兄弟
My interests are strictly pharmaceutical, brother.
你揣着枪是几个意思 哥们
Any reason why you packin' heat, brah?
我身上带着钱
I'm carrying money.
不想被哪个拿刀的家伙给劫了
Hate to lose it to a man with a knife.
他是警察
He's a cop.
你是警察吗
Are you a cop?
不是 你是吗
Nah. Are you?
清空你口袋 警长
Run your pockets, Chief.
让我们看看你的警徽
Let's check for that badge.
你听到他的话了
You heard the man.
放到桌子上
Put it on the table.
赶紧的
Fuckin' now.
我来这里不是让你们羞辱我的
I didn't come here to be disrespected.
好吧
All right.
老子奉陪
Let's play.
抓住他
Get him.
抓住他 兄弟
Get him, brother.
永别了 混蛋
Bye, asshole.
够了
Enough!
我爷爷告诉我永远不要做着握手
My grandpa told me to never shake hands sittin'.
看看这些肌肉
Look at those bricks.
你不是警察 你是干苦力的
You ain't a cop, you're a working man.
干了一辈子建筑
Been in construction my whole life.
你当过兵吗
Were you a soldier?
因为你干架很有军人风范
'Cause you fight like a soldier.
我尽责了
I did my part.
我是空降兵
I was Airborne.
他们训练我们在飞机上跳伞
They trained us to jump outta planes
最后却坐大巴上战场
and we ended up ridin' a bus into combat.
可不是嘛
Sounds about right.
坐吧 兄弟
Have a seat, brother.
我听说你想进点货
I heard you're in a buyin' mood.
我想要蓝玻璃
I'm lookin' for blue glass,
上等货
the good stuff.
定期定量供应
I need weight. Regular.
比如说每月四磅
Like four pounds a month.
就这样
That's all?
你要卖给谁
Who you flippin' it to?
谁有需要就卖给谁
It goes where it's needed.
我想卖给谁是我的事 你管不着
The customers are my concern, not yours.
为什么选这里 为什么是我们
And why here? Why us?
我在芝加哥的联系人失踪了
My Chicago connect is missin' in action.
我的施工队全天候轮班工作
I'm runnin' work crews in shifts 24/7.
时间就是金钱
Time is money.
半磅七千美元
Seven K for half a pound.
在芝加哥才是这个价格
That's a Chicago price.
五千
Five.
从这里往正北走 高速公路交汇处有一家煎饼店
There's a pancake house at the highway junction straight north of here.
早上七点钟去那里吃顿早餐
Be there, 7:00 a.m., having breakfast.
然后呢
And?
带上五沓现金
And bring five stacks.
聊得很开心
Good talk.
现在赶紧滚吧
Now get the fuck outta here.
坐吧
Have a seat.
搞得我们好像在Tinder约炮一样
This is like an awkward Tinder date.
把钱给她
Just give her the money.
瞧啊
Lo, and behold.
多说无益
People talk,
有钱才能鬼推磨
money fucks.
我的货在哪
You got somethin' for me?
我们一点都不熟 兄弟
We don't know who the fuck you are, brother.
会有人打电话告诉你货在哪
You'll get a call tellin' you where your shit is.
就这样吗
That's it?
嗯
Yeah. Uh-huh.
别跟我耍花招
Don't play me.
我知道去哪找你
I know where to find you.
嗯 知道你就知道
Yeah. I guess you do.
谢谢你没开枪打我
Thank you for not shooting me.
操他妈的王八蛋
Fuckin' asshole.
- 喂 - 好了 准备好了吗
- Yeah? - All right. You ready?
我这就告诉你毒品在哪 老兄
I'm gonna tell you where the skante's at, big dog.
等着呢
I'm waitin'.
你车座底下
Under your seat.
- 多谢 - 留着这部一次性手机
- Thank you. - Keep the burner phone.
我明天再联系你
I'mma hit you tomorrow.
到时候你可以告诉我 你们这帮混蛋
Then you can tell me how y'all motherfuckers
是怎么一天内卖完这批货的
built Rome in a day off my shit.
之后我们再谈定量的事
Then we can talk about weight.
猜猜看今晚谁会成为公主
Guess who's gonna be princess for a night?
你们一手缔造了迪米的奇迹
You are Dimi's miracle workers. Huh?
而那 那就是迪米的奇迹
And that, that is for Dimi's miracle.
为什么是她
Why her?
她让我想起了我父亲其中一栋房子里的一幅画
She reminded me of a painting in one of my father's houses.
带她到后面去
Take her in the back.
好
Sure.
看看这些小家伙多可爱
Look how cute these ones are.
他们看上去就像小鲨鱼
They look like little sharks.
颇有你的风姿 美人
Just like you, cutie.
她咬我
She bit me!
她应该是昏睡状态
She's supposed to be asleep!
非常抱歉 先生
I'm so sorry, sir.
把她撵出去
I want her out!
喂
Yeah?
他们喜欢我的货吗
Did they like my shit?
这么说吧 他们很满意
Let's just say they were pleased.
这样的货还有很多
There's plenty more where that came from,
但如果我们要合作
but there's someone you gotta check in with
你得先去见个人
if we're gonna do business.
什么意思
What does that mean?
防患于未然 兄弟
Precautionary measures, brah.
毕竟被联邦调查局抓到 一磅就是无期徒刑
Seein' as the Feds are handin' out life sentences per pound.
是啊 这行不是什么牛马都能干的
Yeah, this game's not for everyone.
我明白 兄弟
I hear you, big dog.
我会帮你约他碰个头
I'mma shoot you an invite for a sit-down.
带上你的钱 穿上西装
Bring your money and wear a suit.
我没有西装
I don't have a suit.
靠 明天没有也得有
Shit. You will tomorrow.
因为那些王八蛋的身份是你远高不可攀的
'Cause these motherfuckers are as high power as it gets.
我是来见达奇先生的
I'm here to see someone called Dutch.
这边走
He's right this way.
他在那边
He's over there.
- 你好吗 - 嘿 达奇
- How you doin'? - Hey, Dutch.
你把钱带来了吗
You bring the money?
可以吗
May I?
第一件事 把你手机关机
First, you gotta turn your phone off.
然后呢
Now what?
我已经把钱给你了
You already have my money.
我来是诚心谈生意的
I came here in good faith to do business.
我叫迪米
My name is Dimi.
你呢
Yours?
比尔
Bill.
比尔·科茨
Bill Coates.
你带了驾照吗 比尔·科茨
Do you have driver's license, Bill Coates?
你干什么
Excuse me?
放心 让他去查
It's fine. Let him check.
你租车来的
You drive rental.
我们查过车牌
We check plates.
抵税
Tax write-off.
有问题吗
That okay?
这个人是我的合伙人
This man is my business partner.
他是小喽啰
He is small potatoes.
我才是大老板
I am the big potatoes.
告诉我
Tell me.
你会是个麻烦吗
Will you be a problem?
你就是这样做生意的吗
Is this how you do business?
请我来被你们威胁
You invite me here to be threatened?
没问题
Checks out.
我向你道歉 威廉
I apologize for that, "William."
你显然是一个…
You are clearly a...
正经做生意的
serious person.
如果你要补货 就用那个一次性手机
If you need resupply, use the burner.
发个小兔子的表情
Text bunny rabbit emoji.
小兔子表情
Bunny rabbit emoji.
你知道我一个月需要四磅吧
You made aware I need four pounds a month?
哦
Oh.
那就发大象表情
Then text eggplant emoji.
我们知道
We are aware.
如果箱子里的货还让你满意
If you like what is in the case,
我们再进一步合作
we do more business.
现在你可以走了 不要回头
Now, you leave and don't look back.
走就走
Fine by me.
你准备好了吗？他们好像要走了
就好了，看好她
快点，他们已经结账了
约翰尼 你真是不折不扣的人渣
Johnny, you're a real piece of shit.
朱丽叶市  海蒂酒吧
你这个鬼鬼祟祟的王八蛋
You sneaky motherfucker.
嗨 混蛋
Hi, asshole.
他来了
He's here.
- 该死 - 他在一辆黑色道奇公羊里
- Oh, shit. - He's in a black Dodge Ram
躲在树后面
hiding in the trees.
好 我们马上到
Okay, we're pulling up now.
给我上
Let's go!
妈的 他骑上一辆摩托跑了 快追
Fuck! He just fuckin' left on a bike! Go!
快 快 快
Go! Go! Go!
他妈的
Fuck!
手举起来
Show me your hands.
嘿
Hey.
你没见过我们
You didn't see us here.
这里无事发生
Nothing fucking happened.
接下来交给我们
We'll take it from here.
你们也是一伙的
You're on the payroll too?
你怎么认识迪米的
How do you know Dimi?
你找迪米干什么
What is your business with Dimi?
是你们两个混蛋
Ah, you two assholes.
你趁他老婆在练普拉提时
That man you drowned,
淹死在自家泳池的那个人
in his own pool while his wife was at Pilates,
他是我们叔叔
that man was our uncle.
他叽叽喳喳吵个不停
He wouldn't shut up.
我警告过他
I warned him.
- 你知道我们是谁吗 - 嘿 嘿
- Do you know who we are, hmm? - Hey. Hey.
你们不就是被老妈子打扮成的土鳖
Yeah, people whose ma dresses 'em funny.
这他妈的是高定 伙计
This is fucking couture, man.
是我们的牌面
It's our fucking brand!
把他的腿绑起来
Tie up his legs.
如果你们想吓唬我 还得加把劲
If you want me to be scared, you gotta try harder.
哇哦
Whoa!
把这魔鬼杀了
Kill this demon.
这是万科
That is Vanko.
这是达尼亚
And that is Danya.
他们是我儿子
These are my sons.
我的家族和血脉断绝在这冰冷的钢桌上
My house and my lineage end on these cold, steel tables.
召集战争顾问
Convene the war counsel.
不好意思 亲爱的
Excuse me, dear.
滚开
Fuck off.
哇
Oh, wow.
他妈的想都别想
Absolutely fuckin' not.
我靠
Oh, fuck.
没死算你小子走运
You're lucky you're not already dead.
迪米 对不起
Dimi, apologies, okay?
对不起 真的对不起
I'm sorry. I'm truly fuckin' sorry.
她他妈的咬掉了他半张脸
She fucking bit half his face off.
- 其实没那么夸张 不过… - 哦
- It wasn't exactly half his face. But... - Oh.
缝了36针
Thirty-six stitches.
还挺多的
That's a lot.
重新接上他的脸颊
To reattach his cheek.
我做的是风流生意 不是外科医生
I am in the business of pleasure, not surgery.
告诉我…
Tell me...
妈呀
Fuck.
你知道生意是什么意思吗
Do you know what business means?
我知不…不 我是说知道
Do I... No. I mean, yeah. Fuck.
生意就是
Business means
信守承诺
you keep your word.
你兑现承诺 讨客户欢心
You deliver promises. You make customer happy.
不是把他们的脸咬掉
Not bite fucking face off!
- 明白 - 不
- Understood. - No.
你害我损失了20万
You just fucked me out of 200 grand.
你犯了一个错 我却要双倍赔偿
If you make one, I make two.
客户要她死 我要她死
Customer wants her dead. I want her dead.
把她杀了 你知道该带她去哪
You kill her. You know where to take her.
没问题
Consider it done.
赶紧滚
Now fuck off!
我滚了 老板
Fucking off, sir.
我的妈 他气炸了
Holy shit, he was pissed.
何止气炸 他差点把我们就地正法
Fucking beyond. He was this close to smokin' us both.
我们得宰了那小妞
We gotta whack that girl.
我没意见 干掉那小贱人
Fine by me. Let's do the little bitch.
我们面对的是一个魔鬼
We are facing a devil.
这个魔鬼杀害了两名士兵
This devil kills two soldiers.
淹死了沃罗迪迈尔
He drowns Wolodymyr,
一位受人尊敬的船长
an esteemed captain.
现在又杀了我儿子
Now he kills my sons.
你们理解我的担忧吧
You do understand my concern?
迪米在哪
Where is Dimi?
他知道这个魔鬼是谁吗
Won't he know who this devil is?
迪米躲起来了
Dimi's hiding.
他们会帮你找到迪米
They will help you find Dimi.
谢谢你把这件事告诉我
Thank you for bringing this to my attention.
你可以走了
Now go.
来点香槟吗
Some champagne?
你父亲死了
Your father is dead.
被绑在椅子上
Tied to a chair
淹死在自己泳池
and drowned in his pool.
所以这是好消息
So, it's good news.
杀他的人
The man who killed him
杀了我儿子
murdered my sons.
达尼亚和万科
Danya and Vanko?
什么鬼
What the fuck?
你不知道这件事吗
You did not know this?
我怎么会知道 也没人给我捎个信
How the fuck would I know? Nobody tells me anything.
兄弟会对我就像个瘟神
The Brotherhood treats me like I'm radioactive.
这个人是谁
Who is this man?
我好声好气问你
I ask with kindness.
我资助摩托车帮卖冰毒
I bankroll biker gang with meth connection.
他们把我介绍给了一个大手笔买家
They introduce me to buyer with real cash.
我们见面五分钟
We met for five minutes.
仅此而已
That's it.
等等 等等
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
我有这个
I have this.
他要杀你来了
He's hunting you.
找到他了
Found him.
- 喂 - 你好 是凯德先生吗
- Hello? - Hi. Mr. Cade?
这里是行政办公室
This is the Main Office.
今天没有人来接梅瑞狄斯
Um, no one's come to pick up Meredith today.
我马上就到
I'll be right there.
克兰斯顿·琼斯小学
- 嘿 - 今天过得好吗
- Hey. - Good day?
- 嗯 - 我们走吧
- Yeah. - Let's go.
爷爷去哪了 他从不会迟到
Where's Grandpa? He's never late.
他不接我电话
He's not answering me.
我给他发了快20条短信
I sent him, like, 20 messages.
我相信他肯定没事的
I'm sure he's fine.
你没把他杀掉吧
You didn't kill him, did you?
爸 我逗你呢
Dad, I'm kidding.
你相信我吗
Do you trust me?
相信
Yeah.
所以如果我告诉你一些事
So, if I tell you something,
你知道你可以相信我 对吗
you know you can believe me, right?
好吧 你越说我越害怕了
Okay, the build-up is just making it worse.
我犯了一个天大的错误
I made a big mistake.
天哪 你真的杀了爷爷
Oh, my God. You did kill Grandpa.
梅梅 我没开玩笑
Merry, I'm serious.
一些心狠手辣的歹徒在追杀我
Some really bad people are after me,
我不想让我爱的人受伤
and I don't want anyone I love to get hurt.
你和爷爷在共享位置吗
Are you sharing your location with Grandpa?
嗯
Yeah.
你可以看看他在哪吗
Can you see his location?
应该吧 我不知道
Maybe, I don't know.
爸爸 他在家
Daddy, he's at home.
梅梅 待在这里 好吗
Merry, stay here, okay?
梅梅 待在那
Merry! Stay there!
爸爸 小心点
Daddy, be careful!
他们是谁
Who were they?
俄罗斯黑手党吗
Russian mafia?
是的
Yes.
他们在找你
They were looking for you.
这些麻烦都是你惹出来的
This happened because of you.
暴力如影随形的跟着你
Violence follows you like a cloud.
他本可以不管你的死活 爷爷
He could've left you in there, Grandpa.
他救了你的命
He saved your life.
这我承认
I can acknowledge that.
你应该去医院看看
You should go to the hospital.
在那里你很安全
You'll be safe there.
我来安顿梅梅
I'll take care of Merry.
是时候交给警察来处理了
It's time to let the cops handle this.
警察阻止不了他们
Cops can't stop them.
好了
All right.
这事我们之后再谈
We'll figure it out later.
还有 列文
And, Levon,
谢谢
thank you.
你还记得枪叔吗
You remember Gunny?
你那个不知道自己瞎了的瞎子朋友吗
Your blind friend who doesn't know he's blind?
就是他
That's the one.
他有一座乡间小屋
He has a country house.
在那里我们很安全 直到风波过去
We'll be safe there till the storm passes.
嗨
Hi.
你想进去吗 来吧
You wanna come inside? Come on.
- 饿了么 - 永远吃不饱
- You hungry? - Always.
- 你呢 - 我也饿
- And you? - Yeah.
怎么搞的 伙计
What happened, man?
你惹了不该惹的人对吧
You fuck with the wrong people, huh?
嘿 你本可以拦着我
Hey, you could've stopped me.
世界上怎么可能有人拦得住你
What force on earth is gonna stop you?
事情越来越严重了
It's gettin' ugly.
你能找到那姑娘吗 真的能找到吗
Can you find this girl? Can you really find this girl?
我能找到她
I can find her.
我会把她带回家
I'm gonna bring her home.
那行吧 你有计划吗
I hear that. You got a plan?
我要从迪米这家伙口中套出她的下落
I'm gonna ask this Dimi fella where she is.
所有线索都指向他
All roads lead to him.
既然你杀进去一条路
Now, you killed your way into this,
那你也得杀一条路出来
you're gonna have to kill your way out of it.
我心里有数
I figured as much.
我倒是可以帮你一把
I can help you with that.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
我给你看点东西
Let me show you somethin'.
你先请
After you, sir.
好了 今天晚上我就是你的武器专家
All right, I will be your weapons sommelier for this evening.
在这边墙上
If you come around this wall,
是一把AK自动步枪
you see the Avtomat Kalashnikov,
从1947年起就一直在杀美国人
been killing Americans since 1947.
此外 这里还摆着豪华镶钻版
Also, comes in a deluxe, blingy version pulled direct
从萨达姆宫殿缴获
from Saddam's palace.
这边是一把M-4卡宾枪
What you got over here is the M-Four Carbine,
这是反恐战争里的雪佛兰黑斑羚
it's the Chevy Impala of the war on terror.
如果你想取某人性命又不想吵醒他们
Beautiful MP5 SD here if you wanna kill somebody,
这把MP5 SD最适合不过
but you don't wanna wake 'em up.
但真家伙是这一把
But this is the real beast here.
天启四骑士的原始武器之一
One of the original weapons of the four horsemen of the apocalypse.
M14步枪
The M14.
你也许还记得这把武器
You might remember this weapon.
我不想但我确实记得
I don't want to, but I do.
拿着
There you go.
我得把序列号钻掉
I'll have to drill out the serial numbers.
不用 已经搞定了
Oh, no, that's already done.
这些从未存在过 任何地方都没有
These were never here. Never anywhere.
有点像我们
Kinda like us,
当然就是这样
back in the day.
我们那是正义之举 兄弟
We did some righteous shit, brother.
是啊 没错
Yeah, we did.
- 里面是什么 - 不是你该关心的事
- What's in there? - None of your business.
我可以去吗
Can I come?
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
那学校怎么办
What about school?
你最多不上几天学
You'll miss a couple of days, at most.
我几乎都见不着你
I barely see you.
我不希望你有危险
I don't want you getting in trouble.
那我就永远见不到你了
Then I'll never see you.
不会的
That's not gonna happen.
看到这个了吗 这是你
See this? This is you.
你一半我一半
Half and half.
我要你拿着这个
I want you to hold onto this.
我会回来取的
I'm comin' back for that.
好吧
Okay.
我爱你
I love you.
爱你 爸爸
Love you, Daddy.
爸爸 我不想你受伤
Daddy, I don't want you getting hurt.
我很快就回来 好吗
I'll be back soon, okay?
枪叔 照顾好她
Gunny, take good care of her.
当然
Yeah, of course.
- 谢谢 乔伊斯 - 来这里
- Thank you, Joyce. - This way.
- 再见 列文 - 好了 亲爱的
- Bye, Levon. - All right, sweetheart.
“我们的天父”
"Our Father, who art in heaven,
“愿世人尊你的名为圣”
hallowed be thy name,
“愿你的国降临”
thy kingdom come,
“愿你的旨意成就”
thy will be done."
这可没有上帝 亲爱的
God ain't here, sweetheart.
睡得还好吗 大小姐
Have a nice nap, Princess?
我们得停一下车
We gotta pull over and load this bitch
给这婊子喂点安眠药…
with some fuckin' sleeping pills...
哇哦 哇哦
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- 他妈的贱人 - 嘿 动作小点
- Fucking bitch! - Hey, take it easy!
- 停车 - 别打了 住手
- Pull over! - Come on! Stop!
妈的真欠打 臭婊子
Fucking get it, fucking bitch.
他妈的的抓住那贱人
Fucking grab that bitch!
停车 停车 停车
Pull over! Pull over! Pull over!
该死 我的枪他妈的哪去了
God damn it! Where's my fucking gun!
他妈的
Fuck!
Fuck.
妈的跑快点 毒蛇
Fuckin' move, Viper!
妈的 妈的
Fuck! Fuck!
他妈的什么玩意
I mean, what the fuck?
她跑得真快啊
She is fast.
我们他妈的要回去坐牢了
We're going back to fuckin' prison!
你懂吗
Huh? You get it?
我懂了 我懂了
Yeah, I get it. I get it.
- 他妈的 - 行了 行了
- Fuck! - Okay, okay.
妈的
Fuck! Fuck!
该死
Shit.
好了 天才
Okay, genius,
现在怎么办
now what?
你没事吧
Are you all right?
我叫珍妮·加西亚 我被绑架了
My name is Jenny Garcia. I was kidnapped.
没事了 我们知道你是谁
It's all right. We know who you are.
我们带你回家吧
Let's get you home.
好的
Okay.
我非常抱歉
I'm so fucking sorry.
想我了吗
Miss me?
妈的
Fuck!
他妈的干死这婊子
Fucking dome the bitch!
- 你逗我呢 - 是他吗
- You gotta be kidding me. - Is that him?
什么鬼
What the fuck?
我操 是视频通话
Fuck, it's a video call.
拿着 你接电话 他妈的…
Here, take the fucking phone! Give me the...
- 妈的 - 把枪给我
- Fuck! - ...God damn fucking gun.
先生
Hey, sir.
迪米说那姑娘还在你们手上
Dimi says you still have the girl.
是的 还在
Uh, yeah, yeah. We still got her.
让我看看她还活着
Show me she's still alive.
看到没 还活着
See? Still alive.
我今晚还要在农场里玩一次
I want a second date tonight, at the farmhouse.
一百万美元
One million dollars.
好 如您所愿 先生
Uh, yeah. Whatever you want, sir.
我会把她收拾干净 打扮得香香的给你
I'll get her cleaned up and smelling real pretty for you.
不 就这副脏兮兮的样子
No, no, no. I want her dirty.
别让她睡过去
Not sleepy,
清醒的脏兮兮的送过来
but dirty and alive.
就这样先
For now.
- 太好了 - 走运了
- Fuck, yeah. - Oh, yes.
哪本护照
Which passport, okay?
你给了我这么多本
You sent me all these passports.
我分不清 红的 蓝的 还是绿的
I can't tell. Red? Blue? Green?
- 我不知道什么颜色 直接告诉我 - 我们要去哪里
- I don't know what color, just tell me. - Where are we going?
什么 好的 去吧
What? Okay. Yeah. Go.
我全拿上 行吗
I take all of them, okay?
- 你想要什么 要钱吗 - 不 我不…
- What do you want? You want money? - No, I don't...
来 拿好你的钱 拿着
Here, take your money. You take money.
我他妈不想要你的钱
I don't want your fucking money!
- 你可以全拿走 - 我他妈不想要你的钱
- You take all the money. - I don't want
钱全都给你 行吗
You take all the money, okay?
- 我来帮你 - 不 我不用你帮
- Let me help you! - No, no, I don't need help.
妈的
Fuck.
滚开 别动手动脚
Get away! Stop!
明天开始戒毒
Starting tomorrow, rehab.
你只会让我的毒瘾越来越大
All you do is let me slip down slippery slope.
你应该是我的支柱
You're supposed to be my rock.
你知道 就像人们常说的 “她是我的支柱”
You know, like they say, "Oh, she's my rock."
“谢谢你” 可我没什么好谢你的
"Hey, thank you." I have nothing to thank you for.
外面有情况 去看一下
Something's going on out there. Check it out.
你知道吗 你只会纵容我
You know what? You are just an enabler.
他来了
he's here!
好了
Okay.
好了 你的意思我懂了
Okay. You made your point.
现在我们来做个交易
Now we make a deal,
你过上家财万贯的新生活 怎么样
and you begin a new life as a wealthy man, huh?
我可以养活自己
I can pay my own bills.
真行啊
Congrats.
- 你再靠近一点她就死定了 - 不
- Come closer and she dies. - No!
我料到了
I figured that.
你走吧 把钱拿上
You should disappear. Take the money.
过上好日子
Make a nice life.
她在哪
Where is she?
我不认识这个女人
I do not know this woman.
你撒谎很差劲
You're a bad liar.
为什么要赌上一切
Why risk everything?
她有什么值得你杀这么多人
Why kill everyone for her?
因为我承诺过会罩着她
'Cause I told her I had her back.
如果我把这女人交给你
If I give you this woman,
你会饶了我吗
you let me live?
因为如果我把她的下落告诉你
Because if I just give you the address,
你却开枪打我怎么办
then you shoot me, huh?
如果你给我一个假地址 我却杀了你呢
What if you give me a fake address and I shoot you?
两败俱伤
That's bad for both of us.
往南走上57号公路
Head south on 57.
然后我再告诉你地址
Then I give you her address.
那走吧
Let's go.
你认识他吗
You know this guy?
当然认识 他是毒蛇
Of course, I know. He's Viper.
他主管人力资源
He's Chief of Human Resource Department
为特别项目招募人手
and recruiting for special projects.
为什么为了一个烂女人大费周章
Why you do all this for a whore?
再说一遍
Say it again.
说啊 再说一遍
Please, say that again.
果不其然
Thought so.
好了 迪米
Okay, Dimi,
告诉我往哪走
tell me where we're going.
她在哪
Where is she?
那里
There.
她在里面吗
She's in there?
是的
She's there.
你保证
Promise?
我保证
I promise.
她在里面
She's there.
为什么是她
Why her?
谁做主的
Who decides?
毒蛇在酒吧工作
Viper goes to club,
拍下漂亮姑娘的照片
takes pictures of pretty girls.
我把照片发给客户 他们选好
I send them to clients, they make choice.
然后安排见面
Meeting is arranged.
我的专业服务
This is my specialty service.
就像买一套雪地轮胎
Like shopping for a set of snow tires.
她们是人啊
These are human beings.
开什么玩笑
You must be kidding.
你觉得钱会在乎它的来路吗
You think money gives a shit where it comes from?
如果不是我
If I didn't do this,
也会有其他人干
somebody else would.
你还没告诉我为什么
You still haven't told me why.
你为什么要追杀我们
Why do you hunt us?
你有女儿吗
You have a daughter?
没有
No.
那你不会懂的
Then you won't understand.
嘿 多谢关照
Hey, good lookin' out.
嘿 还好吗 兄弟
Hey, yo, we good, brother?
老兄 好个屁啊好
Man, we far from good.
我们介绍给迪米的那王八蛋
That motherfucker we hooked up with Dimi
今晚干掉了半打俄罗斯人
clapped out half a dozen Russians tonight.
听说 他现在要去迪米的毒窝
Rumor is, he's on his way to Dimi's trap house right now.
各位
Everybody,
干他丫的
mount the fuck up!
你们听到了 干他丫的
You heard the man. Mount up!
真好笑
That's funny shit.
弹得不错啊 大小姐
Sounds lovely, Princess.
我容忍不了这种行为
I don't condone this behavior,
但我的银行账户可以
but my bank account does.
嘿 时候到了
Hey. It's time.
我们还他妈在这里干什么 走啊
What the fuck are we still doing here? Come on.
好 我去叫那变态
Yeah. I'll get the pervert.
我们只是为了钱 孩子 和你没什么私人恩怨
We're all just numbers, kid. Nothin' personal.
我觉得挺私人的
Feels pretty fuckin' personal to me.
该走了 先生
We have to go now, sir.
为什么
Why?
过期不候
It's now or never.
那就走吧
Then it's now.
我哪里招你惹你了
What have I done to you?
没有
Nothing.
这就是最精彩的部分
That's the best part.
真想知道你的身体里…
I wonder what you look like on...
是个什么样
the inside.
他妈的什么鬼
The fuck was that?
哇哦
whoa.
列文
Levon!
他们是在枪战吗
Are they fucking shooting?
现在轮到谁完蛋了
Who's gonna get fucked now, huh?
他在里面
He's in there.
射穿这个地方
Shooting the place up.
兄弟们
Everybody,
装弹上膛
lock and load.
干掉这狗王八东西
Let's go get this motherfucker.
你们俩跟我来
Yeah, you two on me.
老大发令了 赶紧的
You heard the man. Come on.
跟紧了 不要掉队
Stay tight, stay right.
德蒙 破窗进去
Demon, put it through the glass.
没问题
You got it.
列文
Levon!
妈的给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
嘿 不会有事的
Hey. It's gonna be okay.
好吗
Yeah?
你就…对
You just... Yeah.
我开始觉得
I'm beginning to think
你根本不知道自己在做什么
that you do not know what you are doing!
别担心 先生
Don't worry, sir.
一切都在掌控之中
Everything's under control.
我保证
I promise you.
我要把你的心挖出来
I'm gonna cut your heart out.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你他妈真名叫什么
What the fuck is your real name?
列文
Levon.
幸会 列文
Nice to meet you, Levon.
准备好了吗 小子
You ready, son?
时刻准备着
I'm always ready.
我的敌人不是你
My fight wasn't with you.
我知道 兄弟
I know, brother.
杀了我吧
Finish it.
抱歉 兄弟
Sorry, brother.
- 列文 - 什么鬼
- Levon! - What the fuck?
你好大的胆子敢闯进来
How dare you come in here?
- 妈的 该死 - 我操
- Fuck! Shit! - Oh, fuck!
这下可不妙
Oh, that is not good.
什么鬼
What the fuck?
- 等等 - 快装弹啊
- Hang on. - Reload!
等等 等等
wait, wait, wait.
不
No, no, no!
- 我可以解释 - 妈的
- I can explain everything! - Fuck!
不
No!
该死
Oh, shit.
妈妈咪呀
Mommy!
妈的
Fuck!
臭婊子
Fuckin' bitch!
我操
Fuck.
操你妈的
Fuck you!
结束了
It's over now.
去死吧 贱人
Fucking die, bitch!
我觉得我杀了她
I think I killed her.
很好
Good.
我靠
Fuck.
哇哦
Whoa.
跟在我后面
Stay on my six.
六点钟方向，即正后方
什么意思
What's that mean?
跟着我
Follow me.
里面有枪手在开枪
There's an active shooter in there.
该死
Shit.
我要把这家伙杀了
Let's kill this guy.
那是怎么回事
What was that?
蓝牙
Bluetooth.
那是手榴弹吗
Is that a grenade?
捂住耳朵
Mind your ears.
准备好了吗
You ready?
没有
No.
该走了
Time to go.
来生再见
See you on the other side.
那是什么
What was that?
致敬一个老朋友
Respect for an old friend.
准备好回家了吗
You ready to go home?
赶紧走吧
Get me the hell outta here.
是 我的兄弟
Yes, my brother.
他逃掉了…
He escaped...
和那女孩一起
with the girl.
这不关我们的事了
None of this was business.
魔鬼得偿所愿
The devil has what he came for.
让他走
Let him go.
我知道我们在公众前要保持低调
I understand our need to move quietly in the world.
但我不会放过
But I will not turn the other cheek
杀我儿子之人
to the man who killed my children.
那我们就杀了你
Then we will kill you.
兄弟会高于你的个人复仇
The Brotherhood comes before your personal vengeance.
明白吗
Do you understand?
我明白
I understand.
嘿…
Hey...
告密者天打雷劈
snitches get stitches.
我的女儿 天哪
¡Mija! Oh, my God.
- 对不起 非常对不起 - 不 不
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. - No. No.
不
No. No.
列文
Levon!
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
我觉得今天可以带梅梅
I was thinking about taking Merry
去看看鸡舍
out to the chicken coop today.
- 你想去吗 - 想
- Yeah, would you like that? - Yeah.
- 好 - 我不知道
- Yeah. - I don't know.
你最好小心点那只脾气暴躁的老公鸡
You better watch out for that old grumpy one.
它很凶
He's mean. He's mean.
凶得不得了
Oh, no. He's mean.
爸爸 是你 你回来了
Hey, Dad, it's you! You came back.
我说过会回来的
Told you I would.
你没事吧  爸爸
You're okay, Daddy?
没事 刮胡子的时候刮到了
Yeah. I nicked myself shaving.
嗨
Hi.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
嘿 乔伊斯
Hey, Joyce.
你安然无恙
You're in one piece.
差不多吧
Just about.
看来他们没杀掉你 是吧
Well, I guess they didn't kill you, huh?
没 他们真的尽力了
Nah. They really tried their best.
你找到那姑娘了吗
You found that girl?
找到了
I found her.
好了 我错过了什么
So, what did I miss?
我和一只乌鸦和一头猫头鹰交了朋友
Well, I made friends with a crow and an owl.
我还教会了一只山羊念我的名字
And there's a goat I taught to say my name.
- 不是吧 - 真的
- No. - Yeah.
太牛了 我还在对着它说话
It was really cool. I was just talking,
它忽然叫了一声“梅梅”
and then it was like, "Merry!
“梅梅”
"Merry!"
欢迎回来 兄弟
Welcome back, brother.
你到家了
You're home.